[{
        "question": "Which answer gives the correct functions of both the cytoplasm AND the cell membrane?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "The Cytoplasm is the place where cell reactions take place. <br> The cell membrane controls what goes in and out of a cell",
            "b": "The Cytoplasm controls cell division <br>  The cell membrane gives support to the cell",
            "c": "The Cytoplasm gives support to the cell <br> The cell membrane place where cell reactions take place",
            "d": "The Cytoplasm controls cell division <br>  The cell membrane controls what goes in and out of a cell"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a",
        "tag": "Comprehension"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these cellular structures contain DNA?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Rough Endoplasmic Reticulum",
            "b": "Smooth Endoplasmic Reticulum",
            "c": "Lysosome",
            "d": "Mitochondria"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "d",
        "tag": "Comprehension"
    },
    {
        "question": "If the cell has a protien which it wants to leave the cell, what organelles MUST it go though ?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Nucleus",
            "b": "Golgi Body",
            "c": "Centrosomes",
            "d": "Nuclear Pores"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b",
        "tag": "Comprehension"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the benefit of Endoplasmic Recticulum being positioned how it is relative to the nucleus?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Being close to the nucleus helps the Endoplasmic Recticulum keep it's shape ",
            "b": "Being far from the nucleus means it's easier for molecule to enter both organelle ",
            "c": "Being close to the nucleus means the the Endoplasmic Recticulum is better at synthesising protiens",
            "d": "Being far to the nucleus means the the Endoplasmic Recticulum is better at synthesising lipids"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "c",
        "tag": "Comprehension"
    },
    {
        "question": "If the cell has a protien which it wants to leave the cell what organelles MUST it go though ?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Nucleus",
            "b": "Golgi Body",
            "c": "Centrosomes",
            "d": "Nuclear Pores"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b",
        "tag": "Comprehension"
    },
    {
        "question": "All of the following organelle interact with ribosomes except... ",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Rough Endoplasmic Reticulum",
            "b": "Smooth Endoplasmic Reticulum",
            "c": "Mitochondria",
            "d": "Golgi Body"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "c",
        "tag": "Comprehension"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are ribosomes made up of?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "RNA",
            "b": "DNA",
            "c": "DNA, and proteins",
            "d": "RNA and proteins"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a",
        "tag": "Remembering"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following statements are true?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Ribosomes are self-replicating organelle",
            "b": "Ribosomes have a double membrane",
            "c": "Ribsomes are coded by DNA",
            "d": "Ribosomes are coded by RNA"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "c",
        "tag": "Remembering"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is the Golgi stack the same as the Golgi cisternae?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b",
        "tag": "Comprehension"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which organelle handles shipping and distributing of protiens and chemicals produced by the cell?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Mitochondria",
            "b": "Smooth Endoplasmic Reticulum",
            "c": "Lysosome",
            "d": "Golgi Body"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "d",
        "tag": "Remembering"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the lysosomes role with in the cell?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Waste-Disposal",
            "b": "Defense",
            "c": "Respiration",
            "d": "Transciption"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a",
        "tag": "Remembering"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the structure that makes up the cell membrane? Made up of lipids and protein channels. ",
        "answers": {
            "a": "",
            "b": "Cellulose",
            "c": "Lipids",
            "d": "Water Molecules"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "c",
        "tag": "Remembering"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following organelle is NOT part of an animal cell?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Lipid Layer",
            "b": "Protien-Lipid Bilayer",
            "c": "Lipid Bilayer",
            "d": "Protien Layer"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "d",
        "tag": "Remembering"
    },
    {
        "question": "The region around the Golgi apparatus where other organelles are absent is called?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Zone of inhibition",
            "b": "Zone of exclusion",
            "c": "Zone of abscene",
            "d": "All of the above"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b",
        "tag": "Remembering"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pick the correctly matched pair?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Lysosomes - involved in synthesizing amino acids",
            "b": "Endoplasmic reticulum - plays a role in synthesising protiens and lipids ",
            "c": "Centrosomes - Provides enzymes for digestion",
            "d": "All of the above"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b",
        "tag": "Remembering"
    }


]